Let's ride to find the cards / Dallyeogaja kadeureul chajaseo
Until the end of this rough road / heomhan i gil kkeutkkaji
Shout out! / Oechyeo!
Metal Cardbot, Go! (Let's go!)
Let's gather our strength, we can do this / himeul moa urin hal su isseo
You and I, let's join forces / neowa na himeul hapchyeo
and fight our fight / ssawo nagaja
No one can stop us (stop us) / amudo uril mageul su eopseo (eopseo)
With great courage and strength / meotjin yonggiwa himeuro
With Metal Breath we'll go / metal beureseuro
Collect the cards / kadeureul moa
until the end of this road / i gil kkeutkkaji
Let's ride to find the cards / Dallyeogaja kadeureul chajaseo
Until the end of this rough road / heomhan i gil kkeutkkaji
Shout out! / oechyeo!
Metal Cardbot, Go! (Let's go!)
Gather our strength, we can do this / himeul moa urin hal su isseo
Let's go! / Chuldong!
Metal Cardbot